alleydog.com 2019-05-01

# Psychology writing using proper APA format

AlleyDog LLC (AlleyDog.com) Web Site Privacy Policy  
---  
This Privacy Policy governs your use of this web site, located at [www.alleyDog.com](https://www.alleydog.com/) (this "Web Site"), which is made available by AlleyDog LLC ("AlleyDog.com" or "we" or "us").  
Your privacy is a serious matter to us. This Privacy Policy outlines the type of Personal Information and other information that is collected through this Web Site and how that information is used and protected.  
Your Consent to this Privacy Policy  
By visiting this Web Site, and/or using the services offered on or through this Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our Web Site and services, this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, AlleyDog.com Web Site Terms and Conditions which govern your use of this Web Site in general. This Privacy Policy applies to all of our on-line customers as well as to visitors of our free Web sites.   
Personal Information  
We may from time to time ask you for Personal Information, and we may collect certain information from your computer each time you visit our Web Site. "Personal Information" means personally identifiable information and includes, for example, your name; street address; e-mail address; SMS or text message address; cell phone number; telephone number; credit card and other payment information; demographic information; year of graduation; academic records; test scores; other information that you choose to provide regarding your academic and extracurricular activities and interests; and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online contact with you.  
Right to Opt In and Opt Out  
You have the right to "opt-in" and "opt-out" of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, on this Web Site, you may be able to elect to or not to receive correspondence from us or have your Personal Information shared with other entities for their marketing purposes. You may also make this request by visiting our Manage Your Subscriptions web page and indicating which correspondence you would like to receive. You can also send an e-mail to support@alleydog.com. In this e-mail, please say whether: (i) you would like to opt-out of receiving all e-mail promotional correspondence from AlleyDog.com in general or (ii) if you would only like to opt-out of certain of AlleyDog.com's e-newsletters or correspondence and if so which ones or (iii) you would like to opt-out of having your Personal Information shared with third parties or (iv) you would like to opt-out of receiving SMS or text messages. You may also opt-out of AlleyDog.com's promotional e-mails by clicking on an opt-out link within the e-mail you receive.  
Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.  
Information Collected on this Web Site  
  
### User-Provided Information  
  
We may collect Personal Information from users, for example, through such user's activities, transactions and completion of surveys and other online forms on our Web Site.  
Because some of our most useful services are personalized (i.e., different visitors may have a different experience based on information they provide), registration for such services may be required (although not all areas of our Web Site require registration).  
You may be able to send information about our Web Site, products and services to your friends and family members by clicking on an "E-mail to Friend" or similar button on our Web Site or in one of our e-mails. In some of these cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and e-mail address of your friend or family member to us, and such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.  
  
### Marketing Lists  
  
From time to time, we obtain lists of people who may be interested in our products and services from third-party marketing list suppliers. We may use these lists to send direct marketing promotions by e-mail. If you do not wish to receive future promotions via e-mail, please follow the instructions in the  **Right to Opt In and Opt Out**  section above.  
  
### Web Site Usage Information  
  
### Cookies  
  
We may use "cookies" to keep, and sometimes track, information about you, and to create a personalized Web experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on our Web Site and what you look at and purchase. By using this Web Site, you agree to our use of cookies in this way.  
Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Web Site or certain areas or features of the Web Site  
  
### Clear GIFs  
  
We may use "clear GIFs" (a/k/a "Web beacons" or "pixel tags") or similar technologies, on the Web Site and/or in our communications (e.g., in our HTML-based e-mails) which enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received or opened a message. This allows us to know the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  
  
### IP Address and Clickstream Data  
  
Our server may automatically collect data about your server's Internet address when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you're on the Internet. In addition to logging your IP Address and sometimes your domain name, our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another Web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Web Site; how long you stay on this Web Site, the Web site you visit after this Web Site; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about your computer and its settings; any search terms you have entered on this Web Site or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data.  
  
### Matching Web Site Usage Information and Personal Information  
  
Web Site Usage Information may be tracked in both aggregate form and at an individual user level. We may also match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Web Site Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties. We may also analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Web Site and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.  
Any or all of these activities with regard to Web Site Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.  
How Personal Information is Used  
We may use your Personal Information, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings (for example, to process your orders and respond to your requests and inquiries). We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. In addition, we may send you e-mail notices and offers and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt-out of receiving such notices and offers from us, at any time, by following the instructions in the Right to Opt In and Opt Out section above   
  
### Targeted Advertising  
  
Advertisements and other content displayed or transmitted to you on or through the Web Site may be customized to your interests and preferences, based on your Personal Information and Web Site Usage Information, including (but not limited to) non-personally identifying information, which we may obtain from you or from other sources.  
  
### Public Forums  
  
When you contribute to a public area or feature of our Web Site, such as a chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, wiki or other open forum, the information that you submit will be made available to the general public. Therefore, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive information to such areas of our Web Site, including your full name, home address, phone number, financial information or any other information that would enable other users to locate you or contact you.  
  
### Third Party Offers  
  
We may provide visitors an opportunity to receive offers from other third parties who have services, products and offers that we think might be of interest to you. Unless you instruct us not to do so, we may from time to time provide your Personal Information to these entities so that they may send you such offers. If you change your mind and no longer want us to share your Personal Information with such entities, follow the instructions to opt-out in the Right to Opt In and Opt Out section above.  
  
### Schools  
  
AlleyDog.com works with schools and institutions to provide programs such as test preparation, graduate school admissions, and college counseling. Your school, district, or state may arrange for your participation in these programs and may purchase products on your behalf. We may share the Personal Information that you provide to us through your participation in these school programs with your school, district and your parents. In addition, your school may require us to share your information with others legally entitled to access your academic records, such as your state department of education.  
  
### Service Providers  
  
We may use third party partners, affiliates and service providers to help operate our Web Site and deliver our products and services, and we may share your information with such third parties for such purposes. These third parties are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any other way.  
  
### Aggregate Statistics  
  
We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Web Site and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data that do not describe or identify any individual user.  
  
### Your Access Rights  
  
You may review and correct the Personal Information that is accessible to you in your user account on this Web Site by logging into the membership area.  
  
### Third Party "Linked-To" Web Sites  
  
When you are on our Web Site you may be able to visit or link to other sites not operated by us. We do not control such sites and we are not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other Web sites, and we encourage you to read the posted privacy policies of such sites.  
  
### Legally Compelled Disclosures  
  
We may disclose user information when compelled to do so by government authorities or otherwise as required or permitted by law, such as to respond to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interfering with our rights or property, other customers or users of the Web Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.  
  
### Business Transfer  
  
In the event that AlleyDog.com or all or a portion of its business, or one or more of its divisions, is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.  
Security  
AlleyDog.com will take steps to protect the security and integrity of all sensitive Personal Information provided to us. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.  
If you contact us by e-mail or a "contact us" or similar feature on our Web Site, your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.  
You may be able to create an account on our Web Site with a username and password. If so, you are responsible for protecting your account password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of the Web Site by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you.  
In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us at support@alleydog.com.   
Changes to this Privacy Policy  
AlleyDog.com reserves the right to change, update or remove this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Web Site by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Web Site. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of, or obtain your consent to, changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Web Site or sending you an e-mail.  
  
### Consent to Processing  
  
By providing Personal Information to this Web Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, in accordance with United States law.  
Contact Us  
If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us at [support@alleydog.com](mailto:support@alleydog.com) or at the following address:  
AlleyDog LLC  
PMB 112  
3608-200 Davis Dr.  
Morrisville, NC 27560
